<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2017 on XinW Lab</title>
    <link>/tags/2017/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2017 on XinW Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Regeneration of cortical tissue from brain injury by implantation of defined molecular gradient of semaphorin 3A.</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/12/11/bio_ww/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/12/11/bio_ww/</guid>
      <description>Author Zhen Xua, Wang W, Yutian Ren, Wenchong Zhang, Peilin Fang, Linfeng Huang, XinWang, Peng Shi.
Biomaterials 2018
Abstract Despite great efforts in the exploration of therapeutic strategies for treating brain injuries, it is still challenging to regenerate neural tissues and to restore the lost function within an injured brain. In this report, we employed a tissue engineering approach to regenerate cortical tissue from brain injury by implantation of defined semaphorin 3A (Sema3A) gradient packaged in a hydrogel based device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consensus molecular subtypes of colorectal cancer are recapitulated in in vitro and in vivo models.</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/09/cd_wx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/09/cd_wx/</guid>
      <description>Author Linnekamp JF†, van Hooff SR†, Prasetyanti PR, Kandimalla R, Buikhuisen JY, Fessler E, Ramesh P, Lee KAST, van Bochove GGW, de Jong JH, Cameron K, van Leersum R, Rodermond HM, Franitza M, Nürnberg P, Mangiapane LR, Wang X, Clevers H, Vermeulen L, Stassi G and Medema JP.
Cell Death and Differentiation 2018, doi:10.1038/s41418-017-0011-5
Abstract Colorectal cancer (CRC) is a highly heterogeneous disease both from a molecular and clinical perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome-wide Discovery of a Novel Gene-expression Signature for the Identification of Lymph Node Metastasis in Esophageal Squamous Cell Carcinoma.</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/09/10/ann_gao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/09/10/ann_gao/</guid>
      <description>Author Fuminori Sonohara; Feng Gao; Naoki Iwata; Mitsuro Kanda; Masahiko Koike; Naoki Takahashi; Yasuhide Yamada; Yasuhiro Kodera; Xin Wang; Ajay Goel
Annals of Surgery 2017, doi:10.1097/SLA.0000000000002622
Objective This study aimed to develop a gene-expression signature for identification of lymph node (LN) metastasis in esophageal squamous cell carcinoma (ESCC) patients.
Summary of Background Data LN metastasis is recognized as the most important independent risk factor for therapeutic decision-making of ESCC patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers in 2016-09 to 2017-09</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/08/10/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/08/10/2017/</guid>
      <description>Ozawa T†, Kandimalla R†, Gao F†, Nozawa H, Hata K, Nagata H, Okada S, Izumi D, Baba H, Fleshman J, Wang X, Watanabe T, Goel A, A microRNA Signature Associated With Metastasis of T1 Colorectal Tumors to Lymph Nodes, Gastroenterology 2017, doi: 10.1053/j.gastro.2017.11.275
 Wang Y, Lin X, Chen X, Chen X, Xu Z, Zhang W, Liao Q, Duan X, Wang X, Liu M, Wang F, He J &amp;amp; Shi P, Tetherless near-infrared control of brain activity in behaving animals using fully implantable upconversion microdevices, Biomaterials 2017, 142, 136-148, doi: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>