<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>XinW Lab</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on XinW Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome-wide discovery and identification of a novel miRNA signature for recurrence prediction in stage II and III colorectal cancer</title>
      <link>/blog/ccr_gao/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/ccr_gao/</guid>
      <description>Author Kandimalla R†, Gao F†, Matsuyama T, Ishikawa T, Uetake H, Takahashi N, Yamada Y, Becerra C, Kopetz S, Wang X* and Goel A*.
Clin Cancer Res 2018 Purpose The current TNM (Tumor Node Metastasis) staging system is inadequate at identifying high-risk colorectal cancer (CRC) patients. Using a systematic and comprehensive-biomarker discovery and validation approach, we aimed to identify a miRNA-recurrence classifier (MRC) that can improve upon the current TNM-staging as well as superior to currently offered molecular assays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regeneration of cortical tissue from brain injury by implantation of defined molecular gradient of semaphorin 3A.</title>
      <link>/blog/bio_ww/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/bio_ww/</guid>
      <description>Author Zhen Xua, Wang W, Yutian Ren, Wenchong Zhang, Peilin Fang, Linfeng Huang, XinWang, Peng Shi.
Biomaterials 2018
Abstract Despite great efforts in the exploration of therapeutic strategies for treating brain injuries, it is still challenging to regenerate neural tissues and to restore the lost function within an injured brain. In this report, we employed a tissue engineering approach to regenerate cortical tissue from brain injury by implantation of defined semaphorin 3A (Sema3A) gradient packaged in a hydrogel based device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consensus molecular subtypes of colorectal cancer are recapitulated in in vitro and in vivo models.</title>
      <link>/blog/cd_wx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cd_wx/</guid>
      <description>Author Linnekamp JF†, van Hooff SR†, Prasetyanti PR, Kandimalla R, Buikhuisen JY, Fessler E, Ramesh P, Lee KAST, van Bochove GGW, de Jong JH, Cameron K, van Leersum R, Rodermond HM, Franitza M, Nürnberg P, Mangiapane LR, Wang X, Clevers H, Vermeulen L, Stassi G and Medema JP.
Cell Death and Differentiation 2018, doi:10.1038/s41418-017-0011-5
Abstract Colorectal cancer (CRC) is a highly heterogeneous disease both from a molecular and clinical perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genome-wide Discovery of a Novel Gene-expression Signature for the Identification of Lymph Node Metastasis in Esophageal Squamous Cell Carcinoma.</title>
      <link>/blog/ann_gao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/ann_gao/</guid>
      <description>Author Fuminori Sonohara; Feng Gao; Naoki Iwata; Mitsuro Kanda; Masahiko Koike; Naoki Takahashi; Yasuhide Yamada; Yasuhiro Kodera; Xin Wang; Ajay Goel
Annals of Surgery 2017, doi:10.1097/SLA.0000000000002622
Objective This study aimed to develop a gene-expression signature for identification of lymph node (LN) metastasis in esophageal squamous cell carcinoma (ESCC) patients.
Summary of Background Data LN metastasis is recognized as the most important independent risk factor for therapeutic decision-making of ESCC patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers in 2016-09 to 2017-09</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/</guid>
      <description>Ozawa T†, Kandimalla R†, Gao F†, Nozawa H, Hata K, Nagata H, Okada S, Izumi D, Baba H, Fleshman J, Wang X, Watanabe T, Goel A, A microRNA Signature Associated With Metastasis of T1 Colorectal Tumors to Lymph Nodes, Gastroenterology 2017, doi: 10.1053/j.gastro.2017.11.275
 Wang Y, Lin X, Chen X, Chen X, Xu Z, Zhang W, Liao Q, Duan X, Wang X, Liu M, Wang F, He J &amp;amp; Shi P, Tetherless near-infrared control of brain activity in behaving animals using fully implantable upconversion microdevices, Biomaterials 2017, 142, 136-148, doi: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers in 2015 to 2016-09</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/</guid>
      <description>Fessler E, Jansen M, De Sousa E Melo F, Zhao L, Prasetyanti PR, Rodermond H, Kandimalla R, Linnekamp JF, Franitza M, van Hooff SR, de Jong JH, Oppeneer SC, van Noesel CJM, Dekker E, Stassi G, Wang X, Medema JP, and Vermeulen L, A multidimensional network approach reveals microRNAs as determinants of the mesenchymal colorectal cancer subtype, Oncogene 2016, doi: 10.1038/onc.2016.134 (co-corresponding author)
 Masuda T, Wang X, Maeda M, Canver MC, Sher F, Funnell APW, Fisher C, Suciu M, Martyn GE, Norton LJ, Zhu C, Kurita R, Nakamura Y, Xu J, Higgs DR, Crossley M, Bauer DE, Orkin SH, Kharchenko PV, Maeda T, Transcription factors LRF and BCL11A independently repress expression of fetal hemoglobin, Science 2016, 351(6270):285-289</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Opening We always welcome outsanding bioinformatics students to join our lab.
Please email Dr.Xin WANG (xin.wang@cityu.edu.hk) your CV directly.
Program Joint PhD Program with Cornell University Qualified students can be involved in the Interdisciplinary PhD Program between City University of Hong Kong and Cornell Univeristy School of Veterinary Medicine. Detailed information of the joint program can be found here.
PhD Program in BMS and Hong Kong PhD Fellowship Perspective students should also note the deadlines for application to CityU, and please do check the Hong Kong fellowship scheme as well:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Software &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;
DeepCC A deep learning-based framework for cancer classification. https://cityuhk-compbio.github.io/DeepCC/
HTSanalyzeR2 A R pacakge for downstream analysis of high-throughput CRISPR/RNAi screens with interactive shiny report.
https://github.com/CityUHK-CompBio/HTSanalyzeR2

Server &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;
Rstudio server: Click here to access the Rstudio server in the Wang Lab.
Please contact xin.wang@cityu.edu.hk if you need an account.
&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;
Galaxy: Click here to access the Galaxy server in the Wang Lab.
Please contact xin.wang@cityu.edu.hk if you need an account.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>